So, I made a beat, and I wrote a verse.
Like, here it go.
Wake up early in the morning, trying to figure out how to get my point across the many rivers of doubt.
Cause it's got us in the chokehold, a conundrum, if you will.
If we move, we are a target, but get killed sitting still.
Sitting bull with a full clip for the people, I ain't going nowhere.
Standing rock, solid steel is what them people do.
They've done it for millennia.
Palestinian, Algonquin, Oaxacan, Maori, Gulli, Geechee, Aboriginian, Kulsa, Senosa.
We know the way is to preserve the knowledge, the dance, the words, the spirits, the herds.
Moving through the Serengeti, stay ready, and when you're on safari,
I hope to trample all through the four seasons.
Lobby, mash your dung, the whole system of lies and deceit.
Gave you God in the air to jack the one under your feet.
Seize it, move the new year to train, longer to defeat.
Keep the world in fear, to forget the joy of peace.
All this on my mind, how do I sleep with one eye open?
Ready to receive ancestral transmissions.
4K visions of the end of empire when we vibrate higher.
Higher, higher, higher, higher, higher, higher, higher, higher.
Support a real one.